{
    "id": "6d20cac2e7cf4e698718b515fda97039",
    "title": "Simple past or present perfect tense worksheet",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "e68806a4f8d74152bdc8705c49fe2caa",
            "title": "Simple Past or Present Perfect Tense Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I ………………….. her since she moved to Kolkata.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "didn't meet",
                        "haven't met"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The police ..................... the thieves yesterday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "arrested",
                        "have arrested"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ………………. voluntary retirement at the age of thirty-five.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "took",
                        "has taken"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The teacher ………………. the girl for her achievements.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "praised",
                        "has praised"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "When I …………….. the door, the cat …………….. in.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "opened, jumped",
                        "have opened, has jumped",
                        "opened, has jumped"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "This is where my mother ………………. her childhood.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "spent",
                        "has spent"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You ....................... me a drink.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "have never bought",
                        "has never bought",
                        "never bought"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We …………………. a gold medal in Olympics.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "never won",
                        "have never won"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………….. to New Zealand.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "never went",
                        "have never been"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ………………… in",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "graduated",
                        "has graduated"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}